linoxide.com 2018-12-30

# PRIVACY

You can visit Linoxide by revealing who you are when posting articles, tutorials and other documents which are related to open source software’s such as Linux and Ubuntu. You will provide to give personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you. Information collected from you over the internet will not be provided to any third party so as to put ads on your email. If you will also wish that we do not USE this information for further contacting with you we will always respect your wishes.

## Information Security and Quality

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have tried to implement appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of certain forms of information, to help keep that information secure, accurate, current, and complete.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested.

## Type of Information at Linoxide

Personal information – This is any information that we could use to identify an individual. It does not include personal information that is encoded or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public information.

Sensitive Information- This information that meets the “personal information ” criteria and reveals race, political opinions, religious beliefs and trade union membership, concerns information about social security or information on criminal or administrative proceedings other that in the context of pending legal proceedings.

## How does Linoxide collect information

Submit your email and get updates- when you submit your email to Linoxide you will be receiving our Free Articles in your website.

Sending replies to any article or document – You can reply by giving your comment about the article and you will find that you email will not be published for privacy.

## How we use information that we collect

To communicate with you about our products, services and related issues

To evaluate the quality of our products and services, and to enhance your experience on our web sites.

To maintain and administer our web sites and comply with our legal or internal obligations and policies.

To transfer information to others as described in this policy or to satisfy our legal, regulatory, compliance, or auditing requirements.

Data Integrity – In addition to assuring you that we will protect your personal information, we also want to make sure that it is reliable, accurate, and up-to-date. In order to do that, we provide

## Information security

We work hard to protect Linoxide and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

We restrict access to personal information to Linoxide employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Information Collected by Third-Parties and Your Ad & Cookie

Third parties may collect information about you through the Services, including through use of the technologies for serving relevant ads and other reasons as described above. We may not have access to, nor control over, these third parties' data collection practices and we do not assume any liability related to their collection or use. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Websites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content on the Websites or on any other websites on the Internet.

## Business Relationships

Linoxide contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## We use Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to, how many visitors have come to your site in a given period, What percentage of visitors are coming to your site for the first time, where your traffic is coming from (e.g., Google, Facebook), how long visitors stay on your site, what pages are visited and for how long and where they’re located geographically.

## Compliance with Legal Process

We may disclose personal information (1) if we believe such sharing is appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process; (2) to protect and defend our rights, services or property; (3) to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Services; or (4) to protect the safety or property of our users or any member of the public (among other things, this means that if we believe you have provided false information or attempted to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you should be sent to us via [e-mail](https://linoxide.com/contact-us/) only.

Last updates on: Feb-02-2015, 10:03 AM GMT.
